When a cycle of abuse finally catches up to the abuser,
a mother's love and duty must prevail.
Broken Innocence is a drama film directed by Chase Dudley.
When a young girl suffers years of horrendous sexual abuse from her monster of a father, she finally breaks spawning a
cold, hateful and manipulative teenager, that will stop at nothing, to get her own way - including murder.
Sarah McNeil, played by Sheri Davis.
Frank McNeil, played by Paul T. Taylor.
Lilly McNeal, played by Arianna Harris.
Dr. Gait, played by Shawn Alexander Thompson.
Katie, played by Kiley Opsal.
Dr. Fuller, played by BJ Mezek.
2024 in film is an overview of events, including award ceremonies, festivals, a list
of country- and genre-specific lists of films, and notable deaths.
Columbia Pictures and Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer (MGM) celebrated their 100th anniversaries; Toei Company celebrated its 75th anniversary; DreamWorks Pictures and DreamWorks
Animation celebrated their 30th anniversaries; and the first Mickey Mouse films, including Steamboat Willie (1928), entered the public domain this year.
Alongside new releases, multiple popular films like The Lion King (1994), Les Misérables (2012), Alien (1979), Star Wars: Episode I – The Phantom Menace (1999), The Mummy (1999 film), Whiplash (2014), The Texas Chain Saw Massacre (1974), Shrek 2 (2004), Twister (1996), Saw (2004), Coraline
(2009), The Nightmare Before Christmas (1993), Hocus Pocus (1993), Interstellar (2014), and Tenet (2020) were re-released to either celebrate their anniversaries and/or fill in the gaps left by films that had their original release dates affected by the 2023 Hollywood labor disputes.
These disputes, including the Writers Guild of America strike and SAG-AFTRA strike, had a significant impact on the 2024 release
schedule, with many films being postponed due to productions being halted mid-filming or before commencement.